Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs
1939-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board Fur and Leather Workers
5917 P
26.83 cubic feet
26.8 linear ft.
Photographs.
7958144
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 08, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 10, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5676: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5922: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional records 5685 mf: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records on Microfilm 5685 P: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs
Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America; Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union
7958144
- Able Steel Strike - 1/1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1 photograph
- Bella Abzug (Box 1, Folder 2)
- African meeting, Dec. 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Albany Delegation - aid to Parochial Schools (Box 1, Folder 4)
  9 photographs
- Albany Delegation for Public Schools - 3/16/1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  2 photographs
- Albany Jobs Rally - 10/16/1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Allende, Ms. At ILPA Convention - 10/1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Allende, Ms. - San Francisco, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America - Civil Rights Conference - Atlanta, GA - 12/1-3/1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  7 photographs
- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America - Legislative Conference - Washington, May 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  5 photographs
- American Federation of Television and Radio Artists - Screen Actors Guild - Picket Line - 7/1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- American Leather - FLM at work (Box 1, Folder 12)
  10 photographs
- Americomedia (Box 1, Folder 13)
  3 photographs
- Morris Angel (Box 1, Folder 14)
  13 photographs
- Morris Angel (Box 1, Folder 15)
  16 photographs
- Anti-Alien Protest Rally - March 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  empty
- Anti-Apartheid Demonstrations - April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  8 photographs
- Anti-Apartheid March & Rally - 6/14/1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  15 photographs
- Ant-Nuclear Rally - 9/23/1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  4 photographs
- APECO Strike (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Appeals Board, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- April 25, March and Rally Mobilization - AFSCME - 2/24/1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Argentine Trade Union Delegation - 11/1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- ARO Mfg. Corp. - FLM at Work (Box 1, Folder 24)
  11 photographs
- Arra, Jack (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Vincent Arregovic (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Artisan Steel Strike - 9/1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Ascot Steel - FLM Members at work (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Association of Fur Manufacturers Ratification - 3/12/1987; United Fur Manufacturers Ratification - 4/9/1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Attachment Strike (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Crispus Attucks Parade, 3/1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- B- (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Badillo Campaign - 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Badillo, Herman (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Herman Badillo at Meisel - Peskin Shop - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Anthony Baratta (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Gus Barbosa (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Basketball Team - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Basketball Team 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Carlotta Bass - Candidate for V.P. Prog. Party - 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Bech Roth Shop Members at work (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Harry Begoon (Box 1, Folder 42)
- John Bell Testimonial - 3/18/1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Sam Berkowitz (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Santo Bevacqua - Hollander Joint Board IGLWU (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Bonded - Hollanderizing Members at work (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Borden - Lyons - FLM at work (Box 1, Folder 47)
  17 photographs
- Borden - Lyons - FLM at work (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Borden's negotiations - Jan./Feb. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  28 photographs
- Borden's negotiations - Jan./Feb. 1972 (2) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  24 photographs
- Borden - Wellsboro - FLM at work (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Boycotts (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Charles Brown (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Murry Brown, Asst. Mgr., Furriers Joint Council (Box 2, Folder 2)
  6 photographs
- Frank Brownstone, Manager Dist. 2, ILWU (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Nina Buchanan (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Percy Buchanan (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Buildings (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ralph Bunche (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Sam Burt (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Sam Burt (Box 2, Folder 9)
  14 photographs
- C- (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Ralph Carbone (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Frank Chandler (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Chestnut Operating at work (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Winston Churchill (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Civil Rights (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Civil Rights (Box 2, Folder 16)
  18 photographs
- Civil Rights (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Civil Rights Rally (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Civil Rights - Voting Rights Bill Petition - March 25, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Ramsey Clark (Box 2, Folder 20)
- A.R. Clarke Strike - Oct. 1962 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Cleaning Section Contract - 1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Coalition of Black Trade Unionists - 5/25/1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Coalition of Black Trade Unionists - 9/1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Coalition of black Trade Unionists - 5/1977 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Coalition of black Trade Unionists - May, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Coalition of Black Trade Unionists - 10th Convention - Sheraton/D.C. - 5/23/1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Convention - 3/1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Convention - 9/1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Convention - 9/1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women Convention - 3/1984 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Cecil Cohen (Box 2, Folder 33)
  1 photographs
- Morris Cohen (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Cohey, Cecil - Photos (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations - Conventions (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations - Rally - Madison Square Garden - 3/1945 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Consolidated Strike (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Conventions - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Cosmopolitan Strike - 1970 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Luis Cotte (150) (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Rep. James Coyne (Box 2, Folder 42)
- CRA Strike a settlement - 9-10/1981 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Crown-Monarch (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Cultural Activities (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Cypress Rally (Box 2, Folder 46)
  12 photographs
- D- (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Thelma Dale - UDPWA (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Dauman Displays - Strike - Feb. 4, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Ben Davis, Jr. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  2 photograph
- Day in the Fur Market, Nov. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Dealer's section - Oct. 5, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- DEBS memorial - Sept., 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Debutante Picket Line - Nov., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Judge Hubert Delaney (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Diamond - Alaska members at work (Box 3, Folder 5)
- District 1 - New England - IFLWU (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Dr. Dubois (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Early Leaders and Struggles (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Eastern moulded ratification, 5/1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Eberle Strike - Nov., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Education (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Election photographs - Thursday, 4/27/1950 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Elections (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Elections (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Elections, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Elections, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Elections, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Elections, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Elections, 1955-1960 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  10 Photographs
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Elections, 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Elections, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Elections - May, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Elections - Local 150, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Julius Emspak - Vermwa (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Equal Rights Amendment Demonstration - Richmond -1/13/1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- European Delegations - IFLWU (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Executive Boards - all Locals (Box 3, Folder 32)
- F- (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Congressman Leonard Farbstein, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Farm Workers Demonstration - 2/20/1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Howard fast reception - 9/30/1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Francois Felix (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 50th Anniversary (Box 4, Folder 5)
- 50th Anniversary (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 50th Anniversary (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Luis Figueroa at District 1199 -- 11/1975 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Flim Flam (Box 4, Folder 9)
- FLM at work (Box 4, Folder 10)
- FLM Retiree Center Opening - 10/22/1981 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Joe Florio (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Forest Hills Picketing - 9/1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Forum - Civil Rights - Norman Hill -- 4/16/1963 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Foure Leaflet Distribution - 12/1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Frankfurt Fur Fair - April, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Congressman Donald M. Fraser -- D-Minnesota, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Free Tuition Delegation to Albany (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ike Freedman (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Freedom Festival - March 14, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Freedom Festival - March 14, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Sol Friedman (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Fur Blenders Strike - Sept., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Fur Blenders Strike, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Fur Dresses & Dyers Election - 6/2/1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Fur Fair - March 20-23, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Fur Information & Fashion Council (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Fur Fashion Information & Fashion Council (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Fur Information and Fashion Council (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Fur Market Rallies (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Fur Market Rally - FDR - Warsaw, FLW, May 1947 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Fur Vest Project (Laguardia) (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Fur Vest Project (Laguardia) (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Fur Workers Resort - White Lake, NY (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Furmaster Picket Line (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Furniture Picket Line - Sept. 2, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Furriers Joint Council Cultural Festival - 7/1946 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Furriers Joint Council & Election, Installation and Executive Board (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Furriers Joint Council Elections (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Furriers Joint Council Elections (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Joint Council - Manhattan Center (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Furriers Joint Council: Saturday Forums -- March, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Furriers Joint Council: Weinig Shop FLW, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- G- (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Gangstars attack: April, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Herman Gee (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Gellman Industries: Members at work (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Joe Gemidoff (Box 5, Folder 9)
- General Electric Boycott Rally Demonstration -- 12/11/1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Raglan George, Jr.: May 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Barbara Gertel (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Ben Gold (Box 5, Folder 13)
  20 photographs
- Ben Gold - Photos used or considered for memoirs (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Goldsmith Leather (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Goldsmith Leather (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Harold Goldstein (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Shirley Graham (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Greek Leaders (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Greyhound Demonstration -- 11/23/1983 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- James Griesi - United Public Workers (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Grove Press Rally - April 13, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Grove Press Rally - April 13, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Gutenstein - Prince Party - 5/1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- H- (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Haitian Demonstration - 5/1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Haitian Rally - 5/3/1980 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- E.H. Hall: Members at work (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Vincent Hallinan - Candidate for President - 1952 Progressive Party (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Hartford Furriers - Local 26, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Charles Hayes (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Alan Haywood and Irving Potash (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Lyndon Henry (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Lyndon Henry (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Lyndon Henry - Funeral - Sept. 1979 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Lyndon Henry - Funeral - Sept. 1979 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Lyndon Henry - MGR Local 88 Fur Joint Board (Box 5, Folder 37)
- A. Hollander and Son (Box 5, Folder 38)
- A. Hollander and Son (Box 5, Folder 39)
- A. Hollander and Son (Box 5, Folder 40)
- A. Hollander and Son (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Mike Hollander (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Hollander, Mike [8x10 negative] (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hospital Strike - 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Hospital Strike - Charleston, SC - May, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  4 photograph
- Hotel Strike Demonstration - June 14, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hudson's Bay Co. Prosper Jean Bart (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hudson's Bay Co. - Prosper Jean Bart (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Mike Hudyma - MGR. Local 85 - Fur Joint Board (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Human Form Hanger Strike - 5/1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- I- (Box 6, Folder 10)
- I.J. Fox Strike [folder 1 of 2], 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- I.J. Fox Strike [folder 2 of 2], 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Illegal Aliens - Press Conference and Demonstration - 1/1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Immigration Demonstration - 3/10/1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Imports (Box 6, Folder 15)
- International Fur and Leather Workers' Union - Convention, Chicago - 1942 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- International Fur and Leather Workers Union Convention: Atlantic City, 1944 - Includes Gropper Cartoons (Box 6, Folder 17)
- IFLWU Hospital - China (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Iowa Beef Demonstration - 10/24/1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Iowa Beef Picket Line: 3/28/1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Iowa Beef Strike Button, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Leo Isaacson (Box 6, Folder 22)
- J- (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Jesse Jackson (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Jobs Rally-Washington - 4/26/1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Jobs Rally in Washington (Coutlakis) - 4/26/1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Jobs Rally in Washington (Jackson) - 4/26/1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Jobs Rally - Washington (Wasserman) - 4/26/1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Jobs with Justice Rally - City Hall - 3/10/1988 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Joint Board - Joint Council Market Activities (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Joint Board Leaders (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Joint Board Leaders (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Joint Board Members at work (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Joint Board Negro History Exhibit (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Joint Board News - Spring 1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Joint Board News - Summer 1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Joint Board News, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Joint Board News - 12/1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Joint Board Staff (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Joint Council (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Joint Council Health Exams (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Joint council Members at work (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Joint Council Officers (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Joint Council Officers (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Joint Council Officers (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Joint Council Officers (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Joint Council Officers (Box 6, Folder 47)
  25 photographs
- Joint Council Rally for Israel (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Joint Council Women's Committee (Box 7, Folder 2)
- K- (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Kennedy Rally - 10/1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Kennedy, Robert - Memorial meeting -- 6/11/1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- King, Martin Luther (Box 7, Folder 13)
- King, Martin Luther -- Birthday - Seton and Basch Meeting (Box 7, Folder 14)
- King, Martin Luther - Observance - 1/15/1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Kleinman, George -- Fur and Leather Worker - (editor) (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Klig, Myer - New England District 1, IFLWU (Box 7, Folder 17)
- L- (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Labor Day - Central Park, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Labor Day March - North Carolinak, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Labor Day Parade (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Labor Day Parade, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Labor Day Parade, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Labor Day Parade, September 2, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Labor Day Parade - September 6, 1982 (1) (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Labor Day Parade - September 6, 1982 (2) (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Labor Day Parade - 9/3/1984 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Labor Day Parade - 9/2/1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Labor Day Parade, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Labor Day Street Fair - 9/3/1979 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Labor Day Street Fair - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Labor Movement (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Labor Movement (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Labor Movement (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Labor Movement (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Labor Solidarity and the air conrollers! Strike (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Laguardia (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Fiorello La Guardia (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Legislative Day in fur Industry - 1/12/1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Lepke (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Ruth Lerner (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Lettuce Boycott - Union Label Show -- 6/9/1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Louis Levine (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Dr. William Levine (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Sam Liebowitz, VP IFLWU (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Abraham Lincoln (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Local 27 Membership Meeting - Jan. 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Local 45, Chicago (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Local 46 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Local 64 Leaders (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Local 64 Leaders (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Local 64 and 61 Membership Meeting - 5/21/1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Locals 64 and 61 Membership Meeting - 10/9/1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Local 85 - P&R Reception - 2/24/1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Local 88 - Pension Fund, 1st Checks, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Local 125 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Local 342 - Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workers of North America (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Local 360 Rueping Tannery - Fond DuLac, Wisc. Mass Meeting (Box 8, Folder 23)
- LTV Rally - Sept. 2, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Pietro Lucchi (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Lucchi Dinner - 7/1956 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Luray, Va. Strike Committee - Woolis Gold (Box 8, Folder 27)
- M- (Box 8, Folder 28)
- M- (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Mainwald Mink Labels (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Vito Marcantonio (Box 8, Folder 31)
- March on Washington - August, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- March on Washington - 8/27/1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- March on Washington - April 20, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Marco Factory, Germany -- 4/1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Market Mobilizations (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Marrazzo, John (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Marriott Picket Line (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Mass Meetings (Box 8, Folder 39)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 40)
  19 photographs
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 41)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 42)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 43)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 44)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 45)
- May Day (Box 8, Folder 46)
  30 photographs
- May Day (Box 9, Folder 1)
- May Day (Box 9, Folder 2)
- May Day (Box 9, Folder 3)
- May Day (Box 9, Folder 4)
- May Day (Box 9, Folder 5)
- May Day, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- May Day, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- May Day, 1945-1949 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- May Day, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- May Day, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  26 photographs
- May Day, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Clifford McAvoy - Vermwa (Box 9, Folder 12)
- McCoy - Haricopos (Box 9, Folder 13)
- McGovern (Box 9, Folder 14)
- McGovern Labor Rally - 10/4/1972 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Medicare-Medicaid Rally - 6/1983 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Golde Meir (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Meisel - Peskin (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Meisel - Peskin explosion 3/18/1968 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Meisel - Peskin - FLM members at work (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Meisel - Peskin - FLM Members at work (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Meisel - Pesking Shop Elections - 10/10/1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Menhaden Fishermen (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Saul Mills (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Mink (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Misc. (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Misc. Old Photos (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Molotov (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Mondale - 8/1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Mondale - Ferrraro Garment Center Rally - Registration - Nov. 1, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Monk Fur Co. Fire - 4/10/1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Monk Fur Company - January 1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Monk Shop - Rabbit Material 8/3/1970 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Senator Moynihan (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Moynihan with Fur Delegation (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Murchows - Foner - Kugler - 6/1983 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Musicians Union picket line - 8/17/1983 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Alva Myrdal (Box 9, Folder 39)
- N- (Box 9, Folder 40)
- National Afro-American Labor council - 11/1972 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- National Alliance against racism and political repression - Conference and Meeting - 5/17/1985 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- National Council of Senior Citizens - 6/1980 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Negro History (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Negro History Week Celebration (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Negro History Week Celebration (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Negro Workers at work, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Steve Nelson (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Neuhoff Strike Leaflet Distribution - 12/1967 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Neuman and Co. - FLM at work (Box 9, Folder 50)
- New Jersey Butchers Strike - 2/1984 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- New York City Commerce Dept. Exhibit - Furs, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Newark Health and Safety Classes (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Newark Teachers Rally - Dec. 1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Newspaper Strike (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Armando Norelli (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Nuclear Freeze Rally - 6/12/1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- O- (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Ocean Leather - FLM Members at work (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Paul O'Dwyer (Box 10, Folder 8)
- P- (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Parades (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Parades (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Parades (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Bucky Parnes (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Parsons meeting - March 1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- William Patterson (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Ludmilla Paulechenko Gift at reception for Soviet Heroes - 9/16/1942 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Peace Demonstration - Bryant Park - 5/5/1971 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Peace Demonstration - City Hall, 5/21/1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Peace Demonstration - Livingstone - 4/24/1971 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Peace Demonstration - Washington - May 9, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Peace March - November 6, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Perdue Picket Line - 2/3/1981 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Nathan Perkal - October, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  3 photograph
- Johnnie Peterson (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Picket Lines (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Picket Line - Beth-El Hospital - 6/28/1967 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Picket Line at N.Y. times - Newspaper Strike - 1/1963 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- SSEU Picket Line - 10/1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Picket Line - Welfare Dept. -- 1/14/1965 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Picket Line - Woolworths - Sat. 4/20/1963 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Picketing Debutante Furs - 11/14/1967 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Isidor Pickman (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Frank Piezzo (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Ben Pinsley (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Sal Pinto (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Pocahontas FLM Members at work (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Pocahontas tanning meetings - 7/9/1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Pocketbook weavers demonstration - 11/25/1969 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Political Activities/Rallies (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Poor People's campaign 6/19/1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Irving Potash Manager Furriers Joint council (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Lee Pressman (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Prince Industries - FLM at work (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Princess Ribbon Strike - 2/1983 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Dr. Joachim Prinz (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Michael Quill (Box 10, Folder 46)
- R- (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Rabbit Dressers Strike - August 1976 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Local 150 - Radio School, December 1968 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Railex - FLM members at work (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Railex strike - July 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Railex strike - 9/1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)